export const hintsData = [
  {
    question: "Question 01",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 01",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 02",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 02",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 03",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 03",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 04",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 04",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 05",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 05",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 06",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 06",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 07",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 07",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 08",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 08",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 09",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 09",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 10",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 10",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 11",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 11",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 12",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 12",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 13",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 13",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 14",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 14",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 15",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 15",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 16",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 16",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 17",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 17",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 18",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 18",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 19",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 19",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 20",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 20",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 21",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 21",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 22",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 22",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 23",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 23",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 24",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 24",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 25",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 25",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 26",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 26",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 27",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 27",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 28",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 28",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 29",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 29",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 30",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 30",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 31",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 31",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 32",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 32",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 33",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 33",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 34",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 34",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 35",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 35",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 36",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 36",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 37",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 37",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 38",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 38",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 39",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 39",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 40",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 40",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 41",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 41",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 42",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 42",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 43",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 43",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 44",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 44",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 45",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 45",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 46",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 46",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 47",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 47",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 48",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 48",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 49",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 49",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Question 50",
    type: "main",
    answer: "Answer 50",
    campus: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 01",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 01",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 02",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 02",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 03",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 03",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 04",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 04",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 05",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 05",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 06",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 06",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 07",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 07",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 08",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 08",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 09",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 09",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 10",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 10",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 11",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 11",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 12",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 12",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 13",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 13",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 14",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 14",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 15",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 15",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 16",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 16",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 17",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 17",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 18",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 18",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 19",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 19",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 20",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 20",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 21",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 21",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 22",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 22",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 23",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 23",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 24",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 24",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 25",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 25",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 26",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 26",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 27",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 27",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 28",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 28",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 29",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 29",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 30",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 30",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 31",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 31",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 32",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 32",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 33",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 33",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 34",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 34",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 35",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 35",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 36",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 36",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 37",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 37",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 38",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 38",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 39",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 39",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 40",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 40",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 41",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 41",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 42",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 42",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 43",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 43",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 44",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 44",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 45",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 45",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 46",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 46",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 47",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 47",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 48",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 48",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 49",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 49",
    campus: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ques 50",
    type: "side",
    answer: "Ans 50",
    campus: 2,
  },
];
